Hello everyone!
Hello! I am KANAMIN!
So, here we are again this week!
Yes, today is the day!
The Chotokimeki Advertising Department, to which I belong
will be holding a nationwide hall tour starting in June!
That's right.
I'm going to visit 10 places this time.
So, I'd like to ask you all in advance
I'll be looking at your instagram and asking you about local places, souvenirs, and sightseeing spots.
I'd like to ask you to let me know about local places to visit, souvenirs, and tourist attractions on Instagram.
I'm sure there will be people who will be visiting the prefecture for the first time, so I thought it would be nice if they could enjoy themselves a little more than just a straight line live performance.
We've already taken a survey on Instagram in advance, so we've taken a lot of notes.
I took a lot of notes.
I'd like to introduce them to you all. It was a lot of fun discovering new things like this food.
I hope you will enjoy the area you are going to visit even more after reading this.
Okay, first of all, we are going to start our national concert tour on June 3, and the concert we are going to perform in Seido Koen is at the Kagogawa Civic Hall in Hyogo Prefecture.
I will be going to Kagogawa Civic Hall in Hyogo Prefecture, so I will be introducing various things in Hyogo Prefecture.
I will introduce various things in Hyogo Prefecture.
There were a lot of delicious looking food and souvenirs!
Here we go! I think this is the most popular one...
Akashiyaki - this is very famous!
They say it's delicious dipped in Kashiyaki broth, like a round octopus dumpling.
It's delicious! I love akashiyaki!
Also, Kakogawa's katsumeshi, a beef cutlet with demi-glace sauce.
Kakogawa's signature local gourmet katsumeshi - beef cutlet on top of rice with demi-glace sauce.
I love that it's a soul food that appears in school lunches!
I'm jealous they serve it in school lunches!
And the next one is like the pork buns of my youth!
I'm curious about the juicy gravy, and there's always a long line of people waiting for it!
There are two kinds of Laoshouji, so it might be good to compare them!
Next is "Tomy's Dark Meal"!
It looks like Kobe!
I like that they are famous for their bread too!
Next is
It seems to be a store called "Charwy Parfait".
It's so cute!
The food was very Instagram-worthy, like something a woman would love.
They mainly serve parfait and sweets.
I want to go there too!
The one everyone told me about.
I looked everything up on the Internet.
I'm already getting hungry.
Thank you very much for your help.
It's called "Tacopi", isn't it interesting?
They have takoyaki, ikayaki, omelette, soba-yaki, etc.!
Next, Almond Butter Toast!
This also looked delicious!
It's a specialty of Himeji.
I love it! I love it!
I like almond butter, so I was a little curious.
I'd like to buy it if it's sold at the station.
And also, Akashiyaki with octopus roe.
I'm sure there are a lot of stores selling akashiyaki.
And Moriya Shoten's croquettes.
I like it. The croquettes look good, too.
I like it. It's crispy and looks delicious. I checked it out.
And Wagyu Horumon Kotatsu. I like horumon, and meat is good, too.
And Himeji oden, with ginger and soy sauce.
And oden broth differs depending on the region.
I like it. I'm curious.
And Gozanjoro.
It's a local specialty, simple and delicious.
It's something like Imagawa-yaki. I'm curious about this too.
Next, Gukuru Ippei Beef Slice!
And another place called "Charcoal Grill Steak Kitayama" is also said to be delicious!
I'm curious. I love charcoal-grilled meats.
I love charbroiled meat. Looks delicious.
Nice, thick meat!
And a place called Hiroshige.
Kobe beef bowl.
Sounds delicious.
I've just introduced some basic gourmet foods.
But there are also many souvenirs!
I heard that the gyoza dumplings
I heard that the gyoza dumplings from a gyoza specialty store called Akaman are delicious!
I heard that they have frozen dumplings as souvenirs.
You can eat them at the restaurant or take them home.
I guess you can eat them at the restaurant or take them home.
Also, there's a cafe called Kobe Choco.
They look delicious!
It's a plate of chocolate.
It's very fashionable and nice.
Chocolate!
This chocolate terrine looked so good!
Moist and rich like raw chocolate.
Rich and creamy like fresh chocolate!
I thought, "I'm curious!
Sounds great!
And then...
Oh, yeah?
There's also a potato chip that's only available in Kansai.
Kansai Dashi Shoyu.
It's called Kansai Dashi Shoyu.
The flavor is...
I'm a little curious.
And Gaufre, Gaufre, Gaufre, Gaufre, Gaufre, Gaufre, Gaufre, Gaufre, Gaufre, Gaufre.
Gaufre is a book by Fugetsudo. It's round and cute.
And...
I learned that a type of somen called Iho no Ito is also from Hyogo Prefecture.I learned that a type of somen called Iho no Ito is also from Hyogo Prefecture.
It's delicious, isn't it?
They're famous for their somen noodles.
And there's also an almond butter roll called Enji.
The almond butter is not too sweet, and the cake roll is topped with a generous amount of caramelized roasted almonds.
The top of the roll is topped with a generous amount of caramelized roasted almonds.
Sounds delicious!
Sounds good.
Other than that...
Soda crackers.
That's an unusual name, isn't it?
It's got a light texture and a funky flavor.
I'm curious.
This one, too.
Also...
There's also something called "salt-flavored manjuu".
And Awaji mountain onions... I was surprised!
I was surprised that onions are so tasty!
And leaf chocolates from Monroir!
Yes, I often receive these as gifts.
Those leaf-shaped chocolates are delicious, aren't they?
I like them too!
I didn't know they were from Hyogo Prefecture until now!
This time, I found out that they have roll cakes and puddings called "Koyama Rolls".
There are roll cakes and puddings called "Oyama Rolls" that are famous and I've always wanted to try them.
I always thought it looked delicious when I was in high school.
Then, by chance, a collaboration with a product called Kiri came to the café.
Kiri and this Koyama Roll product were collaborating, so my friends and I went there and had a taste of it.
In Tokyo.
At that time, there was a plate with Koyama Roll, pudding, and several kinds of sweets on it.
It was very tasty, so I'd like to try it again.
And I'd like to try it again. I'm not good with side letters!
Well... you know, I looked this up too, right?
Wait a minute.
Andie...
Charpentier.
Andy Charpentier.
A financier called "Andy Charpentier"!
I hear it's already delicious!
I'm a little curious.
Looks delicious!
Made with original fermented butter
Original fermented butter is used.
It's definitely delicious!
I'm curious about it.
I like the financier, too.
And...
Tacosen...
At the Akashi Yaki Market.
Using Akashi octopus.
Enrakudo's standard souvenir
I heard.
Looks good. This one's good, too.
And Kannon-ya's cheesecake!
It's a Danish cheesecake.
It's kind of stretchy.
It's a new kind of cheesecake.
I've never had a cheesecake like this before.
I've never had it before.
It stretches.
I can heat it up.
I'm curious about this one, even if just a little.
I'd like to try Kobe's too.
And, you know, Kobe pudding.
French strawberry coated chocolate... it looked delicious!
And then I'd like to go to the tourist attractions.
Let's go to Yumeji-jojo today!
The pure white color is rare and only available now!
Please take a look!
And Nankinmachi? It was so cute, like a Chinatown!
I think it's like Motomachi Chukagai in Kanto area. It's like the Motomachi Chukagai in Yokohama in the Kanto area.
It looks like a fun place to eat and walk around.
I read that the food is delicious, so if you are interested, please go there.
If you are interested, please go there!
Shirasaki Onsen is nice!
I love hot springs!
It's in the town of Kinosaki, Tomioka City, Hyogo Prefecture in the Kansai region.
It's said to have 1,300 years of history.
1,300 years?
Wow, that's a big senior.
That's amazing. I'm curious.
That's nice.
I saw a picture of it.
The place has a nice atmosphere.
I'm curious.
And...
There's also a place called Arima Onsen.
What are the three best hot springs in Japan? What are the three best hot springs in Japan?
Arima Onsen seems to be one of them.
It's a nice place.
And then...
Awaji Island.
And Takarazuka Revue.
And the Takarazuka Revue, and the great people of the north, and the western style buildings and cityscape are very stylish.
And then there's Rokko-san's million-dollar night view.
It would be nice to go see the night view after the concert.
Also, it's the birthplace of Wilkinson's!
I drink Wilkinson's all the time.
I often drink it with vinegar.
Thank you very much.
Also, there is Nishinomiya Garnens where we used to have free live concerts.There's also Nishinomiya Garnens, where we used to do free live shows, and the first Marukami Noodle shop.
There is also the first Marukami Noodle store.
And Kobe Harbor Land, Kobe Harbor Land, Kobe Harbor Land.
Kobe Harbor Land is also there.
The blue sea is beautiful!
The Ferris wheel is also nice at night.
So, that's it...
Various foods and souvenirs
food, souvenirs and sightseeing spots
and sightseeing spots in Hyogo Prefecture.
What do you think?
or something you want to eat?
I also found a lot of things I would like to try.
I found many places that I would like to visit in my private time someday, like hot springs.
I have a goal that I want to visit on my way home.
Everyone, I'd like to visit Tuxedo's.
I hope you all enjoy Takissei's live concert, and that you will eat something delicious and nourish yourselves before the concert.
How about buying some food and going home?
If you have time, why don't you visit some sightseeing spots and spend some time in a nice hot spring?
If you have time, please visit some tourist spots and spend some time in a nice hot spring!
Thank you very much for watching this week's edition!
We hope you find it useful!
See you next time!
Bye bye!
.........
I'll see you next time.
Subscribe to our channel!